http://www.fyc.on.ca/privacy/

Videos
Our Location on Fanshawe Lake Our History - Established in 1953 Why You Should Join Us
Current Officers & Volunteers Contact Information Membership Application
Help & FAQ
CANCELLED: Sailing School courses will not run in 2020 – read more here.
Adult Program Youth Program
Help & FAQ
About Our School CANSail Dinghy Program Current Staff & Volunteers Employment Opportunities
June Bug Regatta Jun 12 - 13, 2021 Summer Regatta Aug 28 - 29, 2021 Pumpkin Regatta Oct 2 - 3, 2021
Commodore's Cup Sep 19, 2021 Plywood Classic Regatta Sep 4, 2021
Sailor Search
Annual General Meeting Mar 24, 2021 Annual Sail Past and Commodore's Reception May 23, 2021
Event Calendar
Newsletter Archives
Docks & Shoreline Project
Board of Directors Meeting Jan 4, 2021 Board of Directors Meeting Feb 1, 2021 Board of Directors Meeting Mar 1, 2021 Board of Directors Meeting Apr 5, 2021
Event Calendar
Newsletter Archives
Docks & Shoreline Project
2019 Pumpkin Regatta
Oct 10, 2019 2019 June Bug Regatta
Jun 15, 2019 2019 Open House
May 26, 2019 2019 Sail Past and Commodore's Reception
May 19, 2019 2018 Pumpkin Regatta
Jan 23, 2016 Fanshawe Yacht Club - Race Team 2015
Sep 3, 2015 Family Sailing (CL14s)
Aug 9, 2015 Sailing Season Montage Chapter 2
Feb 3, 2015 Sailing Season Montage Chapter 1
Apr 10, 2014 Laser Sailing - Wind Gusting 20 Knots
Jun 17, 2013
View All Videos
June Bug Regatta Promo Video
Race with Us
June Bug Regatta
Commodore's Cup
Summer Regatta
Pumpkin Regatta
Connect with Us
Like Us on Facebook
Privacy Policy
The Fanshawe Yacht Club and Sailing Schoolwww.fyc.on.cawww.londonsailing.ca
FYC / Privacy Policy
The Fanshawe Yacht Club (FYC) and the
Fanshawe Yacht Club Sailing School (FYCSS) are committed to
protecting your privacy while using our online services. This privacy policy
outlines what personal information we collect, and how we use this information.
This policy may be updated from time to time as required.
Information We Collect
By using our online services you may be asked for information such as your name,
e-mail address, mailing address, phone number. We also collect usage information
through Google Analytics and through browser cookies.
Marketing
FYC's mission is to build a long term financially viable sailing club that
provides sailing activities, facilities, and training in accordance with the
needs of our members and the community now and in the future. To that end,
FYC may use your personal information for the purposes of direct marketing
communications to you in relation to promotional activities. FYC will
provide an express option for you to decline receiving any further
marketing communications, via an opt out mechanism. At anytime, you may
also notify us if you do not wish to receive marketing materials or
other communications from FYC.
We do not sell, lease, rent or otherwise disclose your personal data to third parties.
What We Do With the Information
Personal and demographic information is used to register for services provided
by the FYC and FYCSS. These services could include Regatta Participation,
Adult Learn to Sail, Youth Learn to Sail, Affiliate Club, Affiliate Community
Organization, or a Club Function.
Usage information through cookies or Google Analytics is used to improve
the usability of our online services.
Third Party & Security
FYC and FYCSS do not sell, trade, or disclose your personal, demographic, or site
usage information for marketing purposes. In order to serve you better, FYC and FYCSS employ
third party services to manage and secure data. An example of this would be our
online registration system used for Adult and Youth Learn to Sail Programs.
External Links
This site uses links that point to sites outside of www.fyc.on.ca and
www.londonsailing.ca. These sites will not be covered under this privacy
policy. Please make sure to read their privacy policy when using their site.
Questions About This Policy
If you have any questions about this policy or about any of our
online services, please e-mail us.
Events
Board of Directors Meeting Jan 4Board of Directors Meeting Feb 1Board of Directors Meeting Mar 1Annual General Meeting Mar 24Board of Directors Meeting Apr 5Work Party: Spring #1 Apr 24Board of Directors Meeting May 3
December 2020SMTWTFS293012345678910111213141516171819202122232425262728293031123456789Mon · December 7 · 2020Board of Directors Meeting7:00 PMMon · January 4 · 2020Board of Directors Meeting7:00 PM
Site Updates
2021 Sailing School Employment Dec 7October Newsletter Issue Oct 14Pumpkin Regatta Results Oct 5Club Championship Results Sep 3August Newsletter Issue Aug 18
London · Canada519 · 451 · 8989
Site by Script Reaction
HomeContact Us
About Us
Contact Information
Phone:  519·451·8989
E-mail Us
Officers & Volunteers
CANCELLED: Sailing School courses will not run in 2020 – read more here. Adult Program
2021 June Bug Regatta 2021 Summer Regatta 2021 Pumpkin Regatta
Jan 4 · Board of Directors MeetingFeb 1 · Board of Directors MeetingMar 1 · Board of Directors MeetingMar 24 · Annual General Meeting
© 2020  Fanshawe Yacht ClubA Non-Profit Canadian Sailing ClubLondonSailing.ca
Experience Sailing in London, Ontario
